[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "userId": 1,
    "userName": "Juan Camilo Arias",
    "title": "xdcd",
    "question": "daca",
    "petType": "perro",
    "petId": 1,
    "petName": "max",
    "petPhoto": "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1697722454841-75f9a1fdd8a5?fm=jpg&q=60&w=3000&ixlib=rb-4.1.0&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxzZWFyY2h8Mnx8cGluc2NoZXJ8ZW58MHx8MHx8fDA%3D",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:00:06.241Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "ass",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:01:13.892Z",
    "answeredBy": "Administrador",
    "answeredByType": "admin",
    "answeredByUserId": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "asasa",
    "question": "dasdsa",
    "petType": "Perro",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:25:24.192Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "dads",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:25:26.782Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "adas",
    "question": "dasda",
    "petType": "General",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:47:31.286Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "asfa",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:47:47.799Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "dasda",
    "question": "dasda",
    "petType": "General",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:47:37.336Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "fasf",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:47:45.378Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "dasd",
    "question": "fasfa",
    "petType": "General",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:47:41.445Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "fas",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:47:43.805Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "casa",
    "question": "casca",
    "petType": "General",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:47:59.518Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "dqwd",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:32.527Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "casca",
    "question": "casc",
    "petType": "General",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:03.557Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "dwqdqw",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:30.812Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "fasfa",
    "question": "fasa",
    "petType": "General",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:06.215Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "dwqdqw",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:29.145Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "fafsc",
    "question": "cacasc",
    "petType": "General",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:09.257Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "dqwd",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:27.279Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "qwdq",
    "question": "aqdwq",
    "petType": "General",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:12.685Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "qwdq",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:25.516Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "qcwc",
    "question": "cqcq",
    "petType": "General",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:16.162Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "cacs",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:23.085Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "userId": 5,
    "userName": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "title": "wqf",
    "question": "cqwcqw",
    "petType": "General",
    "petId": null,
    "petName": null,
    "petPhoto": null,
    "createdAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:19.192Z",
    "status": "answered",
    "answer": "cas",
    "answeredAt": "2025-12-12T21:48:21.342Z",
    "answeredBy": "Veterinario Prueba",
    "answeredByType": "veterinarian",
    "answeredByUserId": 5
  }
]